{
    "id": "9d188560ae0e48a5b1c346786ee382f0",
    "title": "Present Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Water …………………………… at 100 degree Celsius.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boil",
                "boils",
                "is boiling"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b37b39b5cf8c44bc9327f9f714a5ce6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… tennis every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "plays",
                "am playing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d2184b474c374f07a00f9769555a3549"
        },
        {
            "question": "The earth ……………………………. around the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "move",
                "moves",
                "is moving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cb7a306f15748c29031922dd82dabd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "James …………………………………. for an insurance company.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c3ee851c9a3422e826ca76a3c3e749c"
        },
        {
            "question": "In Act I, Hamlet ……………………………….. the ghost of his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "meets",
                "has met"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ce6775a607b47d7bb7a03dad55b061c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The kettle ……………………………….. Shall I make tea?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boil",
                "boils",
                "is boiling"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "503cb55a1aac4564a5e44182dca507b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. this song very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "am liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c5710ab82557444586c39fcf33664371"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………………. to the theater this evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "are going",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89fb08c7c1ca432a99eb7c70768d6d88"
        },
        {
            "question": "His train ……………………………… at",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "arrives",
                "is arriving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c460ebe8315745b4b7f57457c98140f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you when I …………………………….. home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "gets",
                "am getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "735307cfb9dd4fd3b09eb27cdfa33167"
        }
    ]
}